Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Media, 1906-2014
  - 6. Software, 1982-2004
    - Floppy Disk, 1982-2001
      - 5 1/4", 1982-1992
        - 9-8-01 Disk 1 - Copy of files on Eaton hard drive up to TASM.ext, Undated; FD-844 (Box 70)
        - 9-8-01 Disk 2 - Copy of files on Eaton hard drive up to TASM.ext, Undated; FD-845 (Box 70)
        - Apple BASIC date file programming backup copy, Undated; FD-923 (Box 38)
        - Apple Works Startup Disk Copy #1, Undated; FD-867 (Box 70)
        - Arc MS DOS 3.3 copy #1, Undated; FD-877 (Box 70)
        - Byte Paint, Undated; FD-841 (Box 70)
        - Checkit, Undated; FD-828 (Box 70)
        - Copy of S.M.P.V.O., Undated; FD-550 (Box 16)
        - DOS 3.3 System Master, Undated; FD-875 (Box 70)
        - Facelift 1.5 Typefaces Disk 2, Undated; FD-910 (Box 70)
        - Facelift 1.5 Typefaces Disk 3, Undated; FD-911 (Box 70)
        - Facelift 1.5 Typefaces Disk 4, Undated; FD-912 (Box 70)
        - Facelift 1.5 Utility Disk 1, Undated; FD-907 (Box 70)
        - Facelift 1.5 Utility Disk 2, Undated; FD-908 (Box 70)
        - Facelift Typefaces Disk 1, Undated; FD-909 (Box 70)
        - Free Sectors, Undated; FD-842 (Box 70)
          T Locksmith 5.0 - T LPL Test - T LPL DFLT - For Locksm B Locksmith 4.1 - B Locksmith 5.0-FAS
        - KB Test 1 - KB Test 2, Undated; FD-830 (Box 70)
        - MB user manual backup disk, Undated; FD-634 (Box 16)
        - Microsoft Mouse Menus working disk, Undated; FD-894 (Box 70)
        - Microsoft Mouse Setup working disk, Undated; FD-893 (Box 70)
        - Modular Circuit Technology Utility Diskette, Undated; FD-914 (Box 70)
        - Moog L09, Undated; FD-843 (Box 70)
          Serpentine - Starclones - Skybombers II
        - Moogbasic .1 - DOS 3.3, Undated; FD-874 (Box 70)
        - Moogwork 5.2 - briefcase work, Undated; FD-640 (Box 16)
        - Net, Undated; FD-829 (Box 70)
        - Print Shop, Undated; FD-832 (Box 70)
        - ProDOS User's Disk - ProDOS 1.0 Based Util., Undated; FD-870 (Box 70)
        - Ultima IV S1 S2, Undated; FD-839 (Box 70)
        - Ultima IV S3 S4, Undated; FD-838 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled, Undated; FD-837 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled 3M diskette, Undated; FD-840 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-876 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-879 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-880 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-881 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-882 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-883 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-884 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-885 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Precision 2S-HC disk, Undated; FD-886 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Sony MD-2D, Undated; FD-856 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Sony MD-2D, Undated; FD-857 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Sony MD-2D, Undated; FD-858 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Sony MD-2D, Undated; FD-859 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-860 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-861 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-862 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-863 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-864 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-865 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Syncom Platinum Universal Diskette, Undated; FD-866 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled Verbatim Datalite Minidsik, Undated; FD-831 (Box 70)
        - VGA Master Utility Diskette 1 Compro, Undated; FD-824 (Box 70)
        - VGA Master Utility Diskette 2 Compro, Undated; FD-825 (Box 70)
        - Word Processing Disk #1 - First Side Matt's Disk #3 - Second Side Empty, Undated; FD-836 (Box 70)
        - Word Processing Disk #3 - First Side Matt's Disk #2 - Second Side Empty, Undated; FD-835 (Box 70)
        - Word Processing Disk #4, Undated; FD-834 (Box 70)
        - Word Processing Disk #9 - First Side Matt's Disk #4 - Second side Quirk Unpacked, Undated; FD-833 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Install/Learn/Utilities 2, Undated; FD-896 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Install/Learn/Utilities I WPED 013772, Undated; FD-895 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Printer 1, Undated; FD-903 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Printer 2, Undated; FD-904 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Printer 3, Undated; FD-905 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Printer 4, Undated; FD-906 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Program 1, Undated; FD-897 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Program 2, Undated; FD-898 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 PTR Program/Graphics 1, Undated; FD-901 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 PTR Program/Graphics 2, Undated; FD-902 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Spell/Thesaurus 1, Undated; FD-899 (Box 70)
        - WP 5.1 Spell/Thesaurus 2, Undated; FD-900 (Box 70)
      - 8", 1982-1986
        - RNDSHEET.LO; RNDINS.RI; RNDPAGE.RI, 1982-12; FD-728; Hill, Rick (Box 70)
        - Disk: Basswork; User: Moog, 1983-09; FD-729 (Box 70)
        - Volume: Moogpresent, 1986-08-06; FD-725; Tripp, Jeff (Box 70)
          Contains: (1) Pressmeas2. H; (2) Tmonprint. J
        - CMI System Disk Version 1.25 (with Page "R") (Fast AIC triggering), Undated; FD-726 (Box 70)
        - Unlabeled ADP disk, Undated; FD-727 (Box 70)
    - CD, 1995-2004
      - MOS Memory Commercial and Military Specifications CD-ROM, 1995-1996; CD-3947; Texas Instruments (Box 70)
        SMYZ001
      - Electronic Data Book, 1997; CD-3951; Allegro MicroSystems, Inc. (Box 70)
        AMS-702B-Z
      - SII Components CD-ROM Catalog, 1997; CD-3948; Seiko Instruments, Inc. (Box 70)
      - Holtek Showcase, 1998; CD-3950; Holtek Microelectronics, Inc. (Box 70)
      - Koblo Version 2.0, 1999; CD-3949; Koblo (Box 70)
      - PartSpec Edition 5.0, 2001; CD-3934-3938; Willner Warehouse Co., Inc.; ThomasRegister; 5 discs (Box 70)
      - PartSpec Edition 7.0, 2003; CD-3939-3946; Willner Warehouse Co., Inc.; ThomasRegister; 8 discs (Box 70)
      - RaneRom, 1999; CD-3538; Rane Corporation (Box 16)
      - Interactive Music Xpo Event on CD_ROM, 1999-08; CD-3717; Instinct Services Group, LLC; AOXY Inc. (Box 70)
      - Trends in Gestural Control of Music, 2000; CD-3537; Ircam Centre Pompideau (Box 9)
        Includes contribution by Robert Moog.
      - TC Works Demos and Updates, 2000; CD-3532; TC Works Soft- and Hardware GmbH (Box 16)
      - Moog news, fonts, graphic, photos, text source files, 2000; CD-3541 (Box 16)
      - Aladdin Solutions Collection, 2002; CD-3533; Aladdin Systems, Inc. (Box 16)
      - Backup disk #1, 2003; CD-3539 (Box 16)
      - Backup disk #2, 2003; CD-3540 (Box 16)
      - Gerber files, 2003-08-13; CD-3974 (Box 70)
        11-470B_Gerbers.zip - 571 KB - 8/13/03 - 8:41 PM; 11-475B_Gerbers.zip - 219 KB - 8/14/03 - 9:41 AM
      - Work by Barry Darnell - backup copy, 2003-12-04; CD-3975 (Box 70)
        11-470 Rev A, Rev B, Rev C; 11-475 Rev A, Rev B
      - Rome 2004, 2004; CD-3534; Red Bull Music Academy (Box 9)
      - 15 JPEG scans of 17 "Moog Record" jackets, 2004-04-26; CD-3969; Iris Photo/Graphics (Box 70)
      - 104 Songs That Will Change Your Life, Undated; CD-3536; amp3.com (Box 16)
      - Arturia, Undated; CD-3535 (Box 16)
        1) Demo song, 2) report, 3) Waveform samples from diff. synths, 4) P'type program (needs Cubase)
      - Reportaje integro: Acto de homenaje a Robert Moog, Undated; CD-3970; SETEM (Box 70)
      - Bartleby, Undated; CD-3973 (Box 70)
      - Bob Moog: Tribute, Undated; CD-3760 (Box 16)
    - Zip Disk, 1997-2001
      - Product flyer - stuff printed by Clarks, 1997-11-13; ZD-55 (Box 16)
      - Stuff printed by Clarks, 1997-11-13; ZD-52 (Box 16)
      - Website, 2000-07-18; ZD-60 (Box 16)
      - Backup of Engineering Files (zipped); copy of Cheetah folder from Gail's computer, 2000-07-27; ZD-59 (Box 16)
      - Tom's web files, product photos, etc., 2000-07-27; ZD-64 (Box 16)
      - Moogerfooger user manuals - all files, 2001-06-01; ZD-54 (Box 16)
      - Product sheets in PDF and image format, 2001-06-22; ZD-67 (Box 16)
      - Norton Zip Rescue Disk, 2001-10-09; ZD-46 (Box 16)
      - 56k modem script, Undated; ZD-49 (Box 16)
      - Backup of ENG:C (Pre NT Server Engineering Files); old Big Briar website; new Big Briar website, Undated; ZD-68 (Box 16)
      - Big Briar, sell sheet, and access, Undated; ZD-69 (Box 16)
      - Color Moog, Undated; ZD-47 (Box 16)
      - Ethervox 4c, Undated; ZD-50 (Box 16)
      - Image Works, Undated; ZD-58 (Box 16)
      - Meet - PVA, Undated; ZD-66 (Box 16)
      - Mofo user's manuals, Undated; ZD-48 (Box 16)
      - Moog bro prntr sprds, Disk 1 of 2, Undated; ZD-63 (Box 16)
      - Moog bro prntr sprds, Disk 2 of 2, Undated; ZD-70 (Box 16)
      - Moog brochure - ethervox 2 panel, Undated; ZD-51 (Box 16)
      - Moog space ad - Big Briar Moog ad, Undated; ZD-53 (Box 16)
      - Moogerfooger demos - Audio: .wav and .mp2; .txt file-descriptions, Undated; ZD-65 (Box 16)
      - Scans for color Moog, Undated; ZD-56 (Box 16)
      - The Alpha Group, Undated; ZD-61 (Box 16)
      - Unlabeled Big Briar disk (MAC100 Iomega), Undated; ZD-57 (Box 16)
      - Unlabeled Big Briar disk (MAC100 Iomega), Undated; ZD-62 (Box 16)